<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>False on Hilfe | Träwelling</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/downloadbtn/false/</link><description>Recent content in False on Hilfe | Träwelling</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2023 [Träwelling](https://Träwelling)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:48:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://help.traewelling.de/en/downloadbtn/false/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Events</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/features/events/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/features/events/</guid><description>When you check in to public transport journeys, you can also check in to events if, for example, you are on your way to or from them. On traewelling.de/events you can find a list of events that are listed with us. If there is an event missing that you would like to check in to, you can also submit a suggestion on the page.
Criteria for events Since we can&amp;rsquo;t and don&amp;rsquo;t want to accept every festival, demonstration, fair or whatever, events should meet a few criteria in order for us to list them on Träwelling.</description></item><item><title>👥 Team</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/governance/team/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/governance/team/</guid><description> HerrLevin_ MrKrisKrisu confuzd_ Initiator, Development, Support Development, Support Development, Support Mastodon Mastodon Mastodon</description></item><item><title>💰 Finance</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/governance/finance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/governance/finance/</guid><description>The Träwelling team pays all expenses from private pockets. We would like to disclose all expenses here soon. tbd.</description></item><item><title>📱 Apps</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/safety-and-security/apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/safety-and-security/apps/</guid><description>Unfortunately, Träwelling itself does not currently offer any apps. The only official way to use Träwelling at the moment is through the website traewelling.de. All other sites or apps that allow you to interact with Träwelling are not official developments from us.
Third-party apps Träwelling offers a free API that allows third-party developers to communicate with the service. A list of all (known) projects can be found here.
Authorization Please note that if you use third-party apps, we no longer have any control over your data usage.</description></item><item><title>🩹 Sticker</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/community/sticker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/community/sticker/</guid><description>Unfortunately we currently no longer have any stickers in stock. :c
We have printed stickers for the community. As long as the stock lasts, we can send you some by mail.
Please send us an e-mail to sticker@traewelling.de with your address and a digital a digital stamp for a standard letter. We finance Träwelling from private pockets and therefore unfortunately cannot buy stamps for you.
You can buy a digital stamp in the Deutsche Post / DHL app, for example.</description></item><item><title>List of third-party projects</title><link>https://help.traewelling.de/en/community/list-of-third-party-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://help.traewelling.de/en/community/list-of-third-party-apps/</guid><description>Third-party apps Träwelling offers a free API that allows third-party developers to communicate with the service. To provide a better overview of what apps are currently available and what you can do with them, this page was created!
Our project lives from being open source, and we live the open source idea. Therefore, we ask you to link only open source projects here.
Websites Project Link Status Infos Travelynx http://travelynx.de/ public Travelynx is a separate, independent check-in service for trains in the Deutsche Bahn network.</description></item></channel></rss>